all the three IP by NB files.
You're free to collaborate with your classmates,
but just write the name of
the people you collaborated with at the top of the worksheet.
I'll just introduce the worksheets to you guys.
Worksheet 2 is on simple linear regression and
multiple linear regression.
You'll have to just plot a scatter plot and build a linear regression model.
You have to check if it follows the OLS assumptions and
validate the linear regression model.
Then the multiple linear regression you have to plot a
correlogram and check which contributes most to the target variable
and build a multiple linear regression model based on that.
Worksheet 2B is based on
a regression, lasso and a elastic regression.
You have to build all these three models.
Worksheet 2C is on logistic regression.
You have to just build a logistic regression model and
a lot of the ROC curve and you see value.
So the last day to submit will be 20th September.
Before constructing the correlogram,
you can use anything label encoding or one more encoding.
Just convert.
You can ask your doubts in the chat or you can raise your hand
will unmute you.
There will be another TA session four or five days before that it
lines. So by then your portion should be covered so you'll be able to
solve and ask more questions that time.
But if you have any doubts, you can put it in the chat or unmute
a razor hand will unmute.
You can just use the libraries to build the model.
Like for linear regression model, you can use LM and for
worksheet 2B, you can use GLMnet.
You need not build one from scratch.
Just import the libraries.
You can use any library you want.
There is no completion on the syntax.
You can use any syntax or any libraries you want.
Which question?
Three, the OLS assumptions.
Yeah, for OLS assumptions, you can do like three.
You can check if the residuals are residuals for the normal
distribution.
You can check for homosodacity and you can check for the linear
relationship.
You can do three.
That's enough.
Does that answer your question?
Yeah, if you put it as a markdown, it will be better and professional.
If you answer in terms of if it's code then use the code.
Both graphs and write ups because try to add your analysis as much as
possible, not only code.
So add comments or markdowns for whatever you are plotting.
Ignite, you can unmute and ask the question.
Yes.
Inverse, you have professional sense, right?
You need to answer in text form or watch.
Yeah, that's what I answered.
You can add a markdown cell and answer in that cell after each question.
That's the answer your question.
Yeah, Rohan, the histogram of residuals is enough for normal distribution.
But do add like a text cell scene.
Just don't add the code, guys.
Just don't write the code for plotting histogram and leave it like to add analysis of the graph.
Oh, yeah.
Markdown code, markdown code.
Just add markdowns wherever whenever you want to write the text or analysis
and code cells when you want to execute the code.
Are there any more questions or we shall end the month?
There will be another TS session,
four or five days before the deadline.
So you guys should, the portion should be covered by them.
So you guys should be able to solve that time.
About the hackathon, we'll let you know soon.
Do you guys have any more questions?
Okay, that will end the month.
Thank you for joining us.
If any of you missed the first part of this session,
we'll make the recording available.
You guys can catch up with that.
Thank you.